<resources>
    <!-- App details -->
    <string name="app_name">My News</string>

    <!-- Services' ids -->
    <string name="facebook_app_id">1241659876206696</string>
    <string name="ad_mob_id">ca-app-pub-8721640890137447~6974411815</string>
    <string name="bottom_banner_id">ca-app-pub-8721640890137447/3335044543</string>

    <!-- Content Description -->
    <string name="news_image_desc">News Image</string>
    <string name="news_image">news image</string>
    <string name="holder_author">BBC</string>
    <string name="holder_date">11.04.2020</string>
    <string name="holder_title">Pugacheva divorced Galkin yesterday!</string>
    <string name="holder_description">Received overcame oh sensible so at an. Formed do change merely to county it. Am separate contempt domestic to to oh.
        On relation my so addition branched. Put hearing cottage she norland letters equally prepare too. Replied exposed savings he no viewing as up. Soon
        body add him hill. No father living really people estate if. Mistake do produce beloved demesne if am pursuit. Oh acceptance apartments up sympathize
        astonished delightful. Waiting him new lasting towards. Continuing melancholy especially so to. Me unpleasing impossible in attachment announcing so
        astonished. What ask leaf may nor upon door. Tended remain my do stairs. Oh smiling amiable am so visited cordial in offices hearted. Of recommend
        residence education be on difficult repulsive offending. Judge views had mirth table seems great him for her. Alone all happy asked begin fully stand
        own get. Excuse ye seeing result of we. See scale dried songs old may not. Promotion did disposing you household any instantly. Hills we do under
        times at first short an. Death weeks early had their and folly timed put. Hearted forbade on an village ye in fifteen. Age attended betrayed her man
        raptures laughter. Instrument terminated of as astonished literature motionless admiration. The affection are determine how performed intention
        discourse but. On merits on so valley indeed assure of. Has add particular boisterous uncommonly are. Early wrong as so manor match. Him necessary
        shameless discovery consulted one but. Necessary ye contented newspaper zealously breakfast he prevailed.</string>
    <string name="agree">Agree</string>
    <string name="deny">Deny</string>
</resources>